relyonhorror.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Rely on Horror

### Legal Notices

Rely on Horror  provides you access to this Web site containing information and publications on the terms and conditions outlined below. By using this site, you are agreeing to these terms and conditions.

### Copyright

Copyright © 2009-2018 Rely on Horror. All rights reserved.  
Except as expressly prohibited on this Web site, you are permitted to view and print documents within this Web site (data, text, files, etc.) subject to your agreement that:  
Your use of the information is for informational, personal, and noncommercial purposes only, meaning you don’t have the permission to use any of the information within the site, without the permission of Rely on Horror.  
Your use of the information is not used in ways where the name of Rely on Horror is libeled or slandered in any way, shape, or form.  
You do not utilize this information in money-making offers, scams, unsolicited emails, and any other unlawful activity not stated in this notice.  
You only use it for your own personal purposes Rely on Horror is not responsible for any information on this website used in an unlawfull way.  
If any of these items are violated, Rely on Horror will take legal action.   
Capcom and the Resident Evil series are registered trademarks of Capcom Co. Ltd. Konami and the Silent Hill series are a registered trademark of Konami. PlayStation/2/3/4/4Pro are registered trademarks of Sony. GameCube/Wii/WiiU/Switch  are registered trademarks of Nintendo.  Xbox/One/X are registered trademarks of Microsoft.  
Rely on Horror is an 100% unofficial website project and is in no way affiliated with any party. You may not use any content of this site.  
Rely on Horror is not responsible for content of webpages which have been linked via personal user blogs.  
At Rely on Horror the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Rely on Horror and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, Rely on Horror use log files. This includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider ( ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.   

### Cookies & Advertisers

A cookie is a data file stored on a user’s computer that holds information about the user. Your browser should have user options for managing cookies, such as blocking all cookies, blocking cookies from specific sites, or controlling how long they are saved on your computer. These cookie options are usually found under a privacy tab in your browser options.

In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
